<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on parlerBinou</title>
    <link>https://parlerbinou.github.io/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on parlerBinou</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Unless stated otherwise, contents are licensed under a [CC BY-NC 4.0](http://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc/4.0/)</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 02 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://parlerbinou.github.io/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>The Mobility of Construction Workers in Canada: Insights from Administrative Data</title>
      <link>https://parlerbinou.github.io/posts/asap-2022-construction/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://parlerbinou.github.io/posts/asap-2022-construction/</guid>
      <description>This paper, coauthored with Michael Haan and Paul Taylor at Western University, is published on Applied Spatial Analysis and Policy.
 There is limited research that examines the employment-related geographical mobility (E-RGM) of journeypersons in the construction industry. Such an investigation is important because migration can help reduce labour shortages and surpluses and allow journeypersons to obtain gainful employment. In this paper we investigate the E-RGM of construction industry journeypersons. Drawing on data from the Education and Labour Market Longitudinal Platform (ELMLP) from 2008 to 2016, we find that while Ontario and Alberta gain the most migrants, the Atlantic region has more than 30% of its workforce that engages in E-RGM.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Impact of the COVID-19 pandemic on the skilled trades: Canada Emergency Response Benefit</title>
      <link>https://parlerbinou.github.io/posts/covid-cerb/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://parlerbinou.github.io/posts/covid-cerb/</guid>
      <description>This article, coauthored with Sophia Su, is published on Statistics Canada&amp;rsquo;s Education, learning and training: Research Paper Series.
French version is also available.
 (Below is the introduction of the article and subject to Statistics Canada Open License Agreement.)
Since the onset of the COVID-19 pandemic, several unprecedented government interventions related to COVID-19 — including the closure of non-essential businesses, travel restrictions and public health measures limiting public interactions — have been put in place.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Labour market outcomes of journeypersons designated as visible minorities</title>
      <link>https://parlerbinou.github.io/posts/visible-minority/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://parlerbinou.github.io/posts/visible-minority/</guid>
      <description>This article, coauthored with Sophia Su, is published on Statistics Canada&amp;rsquo;s Education, learning and training: Research Paper Series.
French version is also available.
 (Below is the summary section of the article and subject to Statistics Canada Open License Agreement.)
Using data from Statistics Canada’s Education and Labour Market Longitudinal Platform (ELMLP), this study examines populations designated as visible minorities in the skilled trades. The labour market outcomes, one year after certification, of journeypersons designated as visible minorities, who responded to the 2016 Census of Population and received certificates in the skilled trades between 2008 and 2017, were compared with the outcomes of journeypersons who are not visible minorities.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Canadian Apprenticeship Longitudinal Indicators: Interactive Tool</title>
      <link>https://parlerbinou.github.io/posts/canadian-apprenticeship-longitudinal-indicators/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://parlerbinou.github.io/posts/canadian-apprenticeship-longitudinal-indicators/</guid>
      <description>We - together with my colleagues Chaoyang and Anouk - created this interactive data visulization tool based on Shiny.
Check out at Statistics Canada’s website:
 English version La version française  All programs are available on this GitHub repository.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Canadian Apprenticeship Registrations and Certifications: Interactive Tool</title>
      <link>https://parlerbinou.github.io/posts/visualization-tool-canadian-apprenticeship-registrations-and-certifications/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://parlerbinou.github.io/posts/visualization-tool-canadian-apprenticeship-registrations-and-certifications/</guid>
      <description>This is a Power BI-based data visualization tool I made.
Check out at Statistics Canada&amp;rsquo;s website:
 English version La version française  Many teams at StatCan publish a lot of interesting interative tools, which appear not very well-known.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Factors associated with the completion of apprenticeship training in Canada</title>
      <link>https://parlerbinou.github.io/posts/factors-associated-with-the-completion-of-apprenticeship-training-in-canada/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://parlerbinou.github.io/posts/factors-associated-with-the-completion-of-apprenticeship-training-in-canada/</guid>
      <description>This article is published on Statistics Canada&amp;rsquo;s Insights on Canadian Society.
 The Daily (a short summary of the article for press release): Study: Completing apprenticeship training in Canada Article: Factors associated with the completion of apprenticeship training in Canada Infographic: Completing apprenticeship training in Canada  French versions are also available: Le Quotidien, L&amp;rsquo;article, L&amp;rsquo;inforgraphie
 (Below is the abstract of the article and subject to Statistics Canada Open License Agreement.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Essays on Family Economics</title>
      <link>https://parlerbinou.github.io/posts/essays-on-family-economics/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Aug 2020 17:17:43 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://parlerbinou.github.io/posts/essays-on-family-economics/</guid>
      <description>This is my doctoral dissertation, which took so much longer time than I planned. The copy is available through Western University library.
 This thesis studies decisions the family makes regarding household unions, fertility, and child investment. Chapter 2 studies the educational gradient in non-marital fertility and posits that cohabitation is a driver behind the gradient. I build a lifecycle model of fertility and household union choices, featuring a trade-off between quality and quantity of children.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Name</title>
      <link>https://parlerbinou.github.io/posts/my-name/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://parlerbinou.github.io/posts/my-name/</guid>
      <description>My name is Hyeongsuk Jin. Hyeongsuk is my given name, and Jin is my family name.
It&amp;rsquo;s a Korean name and is written as 진형석1 in Korean characters. I know that many people who don&amp;rsquo;t speak Korean find my first name - Hyeongsuk - hard to read.2
It&amp;rsquo;s a name with two syllables - in the way syllables are counted in the Korean language, &amp;lsquo;Hyeong 형&amp;rsquo; and &amp;lsquo;suk 석&amp;rsquo;. The first syllable, &amp;lsquo;Hyeong,&amp;rsquo; sounds similar to the English word &amp;lsquo;young,&amp;rsquo; but with the sound of &amp;lsquo;h&amp;rsquo; in front of it, or a strong initial sound.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Usual Disclaimer</title>
      <link>https://parlerbinou.github.io/posts/usual-disclaimer/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://parlerbinou.github.io/posts/usual-disclaimer/</guid>
      <description>All contents in this blog are my own, and none of them are reviewed, supported, or endorsed in any manner by my employer(s). Any opinions or ideas expressed in the contents are strictly my own, and they do not represent my employer&amp;rsquo;s, any groups&#39; or organizations&#39; I belong to.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
