<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>projects on parlerBinou</title>
    <link>https://parlerbinou.github.io/tags/projects/</link>
    <description>Recent content in projects on parlerBinou</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Unless stated otherwise, contents are licensed under a [CC BY-NC 4.0](http://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc/4.0/)</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 24 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://parlerbinou.github.io/tags/projects/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Canadian Apprenticeship Longitudinal Indicators: Interactive Tool</title>
      <link>https://parlerbinou.github.io/posts/canadian-apprenticeship-longitudinal-indicators/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://parlerbinou.github.io/posts/canadian-apprenticeship-longitudinal-indicators/</guid>
      <description>We - together with my colleagues Chaoyang and Anouk - created this interactive data visulization tool based on Shiny.
Check out at Statistics Canada’s website:
 English version La version française  All programs are available on this GitHub repository.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shiny app: Interprovincial mobility of journeypersons in Canada</title>
      <link>https://parlerbinou.github.io/posts/interprovincial-mobility-of-journeypersons-in-canada/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://parlerbinou.github.io/posts/interprovincial-mobility-of-journeypersons-in-canada/</guid>
      <description>I made this interactive visualization tool based on Shiny. It presents the data (Statistics Canada Table 37-10-0204-01) in a nice Chord diagram.
Please not that this is not an official product from StatCan.
 English version La version française  All programs are available on this GitHub repository.
Update on June 24, 2021 This product is going to be discontinued. The above link may not be maintained and can be removed in the future.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Canadian Apprenticeship Registrations and Certifications: Interactive Tool</title>
      <link>https://parlerbinou.github.io/posts/visualization-tool-canadian-apprenticeship-registrations-and-certifications/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://parlerbinou.github.io/posts/visualization-tool-canadian-apprenticeship-registrations-and-certifications/</guid>
      <description>This is a Power BI-based data visualization tool I made.
Check out at Statistics Canada&amp;rsquo;s website:
 English version La version française  Many teams at StatCan publish a lot of interesting interative tools, which appear not very well-known.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Factors associated with the completion of apprenticeship training in Canada</title>
      <link>https://parlerbinou.github.io/posts/factors-associated-with-the-completion-of-apprenticeship-training-in-canada/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://parlerbinou.github.io/posts/factors-associated-with-the-completion-of-apprenticeship-training-in-canada/</guid>
      <description>This article is published on Statistics Canada&amp;rsquo;s Insights on Canadian Society.
 The Daily (a short summary of the article for press release): Study: Completing apprenticeship training in Canada Article: Factors associated with the completion of apprenticeship training in Canada Infographic: Completing apprenticeship training in Canada  French versions are also available: Le Quotidien, L&amp;rsquo;article, L&amp;rsquo;inforgraphie
 (Below is the abstract of the article and subject to Statistics Canada Open License Agreement.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Essays on Family Economics</title>
      <link>https://parlerbinou.github.io/posts/essays-on-family-economics/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Aug 2020 17:17:43 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://parlerbinou.github.io/posts/essays-on-family-economics/</guid>
      <description>This is my doctoral dissertation, which took so much longer time than I planned. The copy is available through Western University library.
 This thesis studies decisions the family makes regarding household unions, fertility, and child investment. Chapter 2 studies the educational gradient in non-marital fertility and posits that cohabitation is a driver behind the gradient. I build a lifecycle model of fertility and household union choices, featuring a trade-off between quality and quantity of children.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
